birejji.com 2012-06-16

# Birejji

Birejji Privacy Policy

If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us: support@birejji.com

Information Collection and Usage

Registration

When you create an account on Birejji, some personal information is collected. The information collected is as follows: Your Birejji account username, e-mail address, IP address, and the password associated with your account. The only information that will be publicly visible is your account username.

Usage

The information collected from you is solely used for identification purposes. Personal information is not shared with any third party entities. Your e-mail address is serves as your payment processor's payment address as well as the only means Birejji has of contacting you outside of Birejji.

Contact

Birejji may contact you to inform you of changes to our policies or to inform you of any changes regarding your account with Birejji. Birejji may also send you an e-mail requesting that you verify any changes made to your account (Example: Requesting a new password). However, at no time will Birejji contact you prompting you for any personal information or passwords.

Updating Information

You may request a new password through the "I Forgot My Password" link on the login page. You may update your payment/personal e-mail while logged into your account through the "Account" link.

Our Policy Towards Minors

Under 13

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at support@birejji.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

Privacy Policy Changes

Changes to this Policy

Birejji reserves the right to modify this privacy policy to ensure the protection of its members and to enhance the understanding of our policies.
